<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Baz&#39;s Clearances: A professional Dorset house clearance Company on </title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Baz&#39;s Clearances: A professional Dorset house clearance Company on </description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 20:14:55 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>A guide to our house clearance Dorset services</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/house-clearance-dorset/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 20:14:55 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/house-clearance-dorset/</guid>
      <description>A Local Dorset House Clearance Service Baz&amp;#39;s Clearances: A …A guide to our house … Baz&amp;#39;s Clearances: A …A guide to our house … Dorset House Clearance We have many long-term clients in and around Dorset, as well as further afield, who we have been helping to clear properties and move goods for for several years. One trusted client would only consider us when it came to moving an extremely expensive antique table, and another entrusts us to move specialist items worth five or even six figures.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How can we contact you? Details below....</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 22:48:25 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/contact/</guid>
      <description>Baz&amp;#39;s Clearances: A …How can we contact you? … Contact us We can come round at short notice and give you a no-commitment quotation If you prefer, get in touch by email Your Email: Your Query: Send +44 7793 251 677 info@bazclearance.co.uk&#xA;92 Church Rd, Ferndown, BH22 9EX&#xA;Weekdays 7:30-20:00 Saturdays 7:30-18:00, Sundays 11:00-1700 Landline 01202 896289 Alternate number 07915019222 Contact us 92 Church Rd Ferndown Dorset BH22 9EX</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Our details should you need to contact us</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/simple_contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 22:48:25 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/simple_contact/</guid>
      <description>Baz&amp;#39;s Clearances: A … Contact us Get in touch for a quote and advice on any house clearance If you prefer, get in touch by email Your Email: Your Query: Send +44 7793 251 677 info@bazclearance.co.uk&#xA;Contact us 92 Church Rd Ferndown Dorset BH22 9EX</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Who has helped us? A list of credits &#43; the site license</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/credits/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 17:45:53 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/credits/</guid>
      <description>Baz&amp;#39;s Clearances: A … Software License For Hugo Bricks MIT License&#xA;Copyright (c) 2023 Joost van der Schee&#xA;Permission is hereby granted, free of charge, to any person obtaining a copy of this software and associated documentation files (the &amp;ldquo;Software&amp;rdquo;), to deal in the Software without restriction, including without limitation the rights to use, copy, modify, merge, publish, distribute, sublicense, and/or sell copies of the Software, and to permit persons to whom the Software is furnished to do so, subject to the following conditions:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>These are our openinghours</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/openinghours/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 16:52:02 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/openinghours/</guid>
      <description> Baz&amp;#39;s Clearances: A … Our Availability weekdays: start: 7.30 am end: 8.00 pm sat: start: 7.30 am end: 6.00 pm sun: start: 11.00 am end: 5.00 pm telephone: 07793 251 677 </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What areas do you cover, besides Dorset, Bournemouth &amp; Poole, etc?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/bournemouth-house-clearance/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 08:17:33 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/bournemouth-house-clearance/</guid>
      <description>Baz&amp;#39;s Clearances: A …What areas do you cover, … Dorset House Clearance We are based in Ferndown just on the periphery of Poole &amp;amp; Bournemouth; this means we are essentially a Dorset House Clearance Company&amp;hellip;but of course we can work further afield. We are available as per the image postcodes [ SP, SO, DT, BH, PO ] so essentially throughout Dorset &amp;amp; into Hampshire &amp;mdash;&amp;gt; Bournemouth, Poole, Christchurch, St Leonard&amp;rsquo;s, Ringwood, Verwood, Wimbourne, Blandford Forum, Shaftesbury, Sherborne, Dorchester, Weymouth, Swanage, Wareham, Southampton, Portsmouth, Lyndhurst, Lymington, New Milton, Winchester, Petersfield, Andover, Gosport, Eastleigh, Havant - and we also can work as far away as Yeovil &amp;amp; Salisbury.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A link to our Google reviews - and also feel free to leave one!</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/feedback/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Feb 2024 15:25:23 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/feedback/</guid>
      <description>Our Reputation Page Baz&amp;#39;s Clearances: A … Our Customers&amp;rsquo; Experiences So Far Stephen Fowlet Google Review Baz made a great job in clearing out my mother&amp;#39;s house. Very tidy work at a reasonable price taking care not to damage the paintwork.&#xA;Stuart Millar Google Review Used Dorset House clearance recently, very reliable and offer an excellent service. I was most impressed and would not hesitate using there services again in the future or recommending them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>cta</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/bricks/cta/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/bricks/cta/</guid>
      <description>We are available on 07793 251 677 On the mobile? Just click the phone icon - Or Send us an Email</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FAQ&#39;s: A list of some frequently asked questions</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/faq/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/faq/</guid>
      <description>Baz&amp;#39;s Clearances: A … Frequently Asked Questions These are some of the most common questions and requirements we receive. If your query is not covered, then don&amp;rsquo;t hesitate to get in touch&#xA;About Us Which areas do you cover? We work in a 40 mile radius of Bournemouth where we are based. So Dorset, Hampshire, and up to Yeovil and Salisbury. Who are your clients? Our clients fall into the following categories &amp;ndash; Home Owners, Landlords, Property Management Companies, Housing Associations, Estate Agents, Solicitors, Local Authorities, and Builders.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>features</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/bricks/features/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/bricks/features/</guid>
      <description>Our Services Residential &amp;amp; Commercial Available for residential &amp;amp; commercial properties throughout Dorset - including Bournemouth, Poole &amp;amp; environs.&#xA;Quotation We work to the customer’s specifications. Just explain what you want done and how you want it done, and we will implement it. Our quotations are not exorbitant. We give competitive, reasonable quotations&#xA;Waste We are registered with the environmental agency (as legally required); our Waste Carrier Registration is: CBDU508787. All rubbish is correctly &amp;amp; legally disposed of.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Here are our details if you want to get in touch</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/get-in-touch/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/get-in-touch/</guid>
      <description>Baz&amp;#39;s Clearances: A … We are available on 07793 251 677 On the mobile? Just click the phone icon - Or Send us an Email&#xA;Contact us 92 Church Rd Ferndown Dorset BH22 9EX</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>map</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/bricks/map/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/bricks/map/</guid>
      <description>Contact us 92 Church Rd Ferndown Dorset BH22 9EX</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meet Baz and Marcus</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/about/</guid>
      <description>Baz&amp;#39;s Clearances: A …Meet Baz and Marcus Us at Work Who We Are We are a core team of two, myself Baz, and Marcus. You can see us in the pictures, or on Facebook by clicking the Facebook social icon in the footer. We both have considerable experience doing courier work running things round the country, (you can see my Shiply profile in the icons), and now we operate locally - rather than running all over the country - doing house clearances.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Our Privacy policy</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/privacy-policy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/privacy-policy/</guid>
      <description>Baz&amp;#39;s Clearances: A … Privacy Policy At Baz&amp;rsquo;s Clearances, we handle your personal data with care and due diligence. Our privacy policy explains how and when we collect and use your personal information, and how we protect your privacy and security. If you have additional questions or require more information about our Privacy Policy, do not hesitate to contact us.&#xA;General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) We are a Data Controller of your information.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Page not found (404)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/404/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/404/</guid>
      <description>This URL does not exist Back to home</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reviews</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/bricks/reviews/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/bricks/reviews/</guid>
      <description>What our customers say about us </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Terms And Conditions</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/terms-and-conditions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/terms-and-conditions/</guid>
      <description>Baz&amp;#39;s Clearances: A … Terms &amp;amp; Conditions By booking a clearance and using our services, you agree to these terms and conditions, which govern your use of our website and our services.&#xA;Definitions “You”, “User” or &amp;ldquo;the customer&amp;rdquo; refers to any individual or entity that uses our website or our services. “We,” “Us,”, “Our” or &amp;ldquo;the supplier&amp;rdquo; refers to Baz&amp;rsquo;s Clearances. “Services” refers to the removal services that we provide.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
